Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 6, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Central Hudson: Serving the Growing Mid-Hudson Region, Publication (Box 6, Folder 89)
- Box: 6, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Employee Performance Review Report, 1961; Publication (Box 6, Folder 90)
- Box: 6, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Program for the Introduction of New Employees, 1955; Publication (Box 6, Folder 91)
- Box: 6, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Pre-Employment and Placement Tests, Publication (Box 6, Folder 92)
- Box: 6, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Physical Examination for Employment with Central Hudson Gas & Electric Corp., 1951; Publication (Box 6, Folder 93)
- Box: 6, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Financial and Statistical Report- 11th Edition, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 94)
- Box: 6, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Financial and Statistical Report- 6th Edition, 1965; Publication (Box 6, Folder 95)
- Box: 6, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Central Hudson Gas & Electric Corporation folder, Publication (Box 6, Folder 96)
- Box: 6, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Information for Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 97)
- Box: 6, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Organizational Charts, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 98)
- Box: 6, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Article I: Representation and Recognition, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 99)
- Box: 6, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Central Hudson Bulletin Vol.38, No.11, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 100)
- Box: 6, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Cadet Training Program, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 101)
- Box: 6, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: News Digest for Supervisors, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 102)
- Box: 6, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Your Accidental Death and Dismemberment Insurance, 1961; Publication (Box 6, Folder 103)
- Box: 6, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Re: Company Life Insurance, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 104)
- Box: 6, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: Employee Education Policy, 1964; Publication (Box 6, Folder 105)
- Box: 6, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Bank Tellers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 106)
- Box: 6, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: Training Manual for Commercial Bookkeepers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 107)
- Box: 6, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Conference Program, Publication (Box 6, Folder 108)
- Box: 6, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Management Record Vol. XIV No.5, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 109)
    Author: Charles R. Hook, Jr.
- Box: 6, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Train Executives While They Work, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 110)
    Author: Robert C. Sampson
- Box: 6, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: Life Insurance, Accidental Death and Dismemberment Insurance, Accident and Health Insurance, Publication (Box 6, Folder 111)
- Box: 6, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 6, Folder 112)
- Box: 6, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Employees' Pension Plan and Employees' Special Pension Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 113)
- Box: 6, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: Official Text of Employees' Pension Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 114)
- Box: 6, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Chesapeake & Ohio Supplemental Pension Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 115)
- Box: 6, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Baltimore & Ohio Supplemental Pension Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 116)
- Box: 7, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Employment and Employee Services Manual, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Box: 7, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Monthly Investment Plan for Employees of City Investing Company and Subsidiaries, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Box: 7, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Safety Saves!, 1951; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Box: 7, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Personnel Education Program (PEP), 1956; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Box: 7, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Case History, 1956; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Box: 7, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Management Compensation Program for The Arrow Company, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Box: 7, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Sales Training Manual, 1953; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Box: 7, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Manual of Operation: Suggestion Plan Revised, 1953; Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Box: 7, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Tips on Recruiting, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Box: 7, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Safety, Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Box: 7, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Manual for Interviewers: Clerical, Factory, Warehouse Operations, Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Box: 7, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Introduction of New Employees, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Box: 7, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Schedule for New Employees, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Box: 7, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Policy and Objectives, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Box: 7, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Pre-Employment Eye Rating Code, 1947; Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Box: 7, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Preventing Accidents is Your Job: A York Syncro-Film Feature, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Box: 7, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: York Productions Cluett Safety Spots, 1957; Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Box: 7, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Checklist for All New Employees, Publication (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Box: 7, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Employee Induction Check List, Publication (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Box: 7, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Instructor's Checklist, Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Box: 7, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: What Do You Think About Cluett, Peabody & Co., Inc?, Publication (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Box: 7, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Organization, Publication (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Box: 7, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Outline of Training Program on The Key to the Future, 1952; Publication (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Box: 7, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: A Case History in Management, Publication (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Box: 7, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Step-By-Step Selection Program, 1953; Publication (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Box: 7, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Opportunities with Arrow Through Sales, Publication (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Box: 7, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Box: 7, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Policies and Objectives, 1963; Publication (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Box: 7, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Employees Group Insurance Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Box: 7, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Employees Group Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Box: 7, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of the CPP, 1953; Publication (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Box: 7, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Employees Retirement Income Plan, 1974; Publication (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Box: 7, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Employees Hospital, Surgical and Medical Plan, 1974; Publication (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Box: 7, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Sickness and Accident Benefit Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Box: 7, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employee Savings and Investment Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Box: 7, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Colgate Palmolive Company Annual Report, 1957; Publication (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Box: 7, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Policy Governing Employees in Military Service Under the Universal Military Training and Service Act and the Reserve Forces Act, 1956; Publication (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Box: 7, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Sickness and Accident Benefit Plan Memo, 1957; Publication (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Box: 7, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Colgate Union News- 4/12/60, 1960; Publication (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Box: 7, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Colgate Union News- 12/19/58, Publication (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Box: 7, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Colgate-Palmolive Company Employees Savings and Investment Plan, 1972; Publication (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Box: 7, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Supplement to the Employees Savings and Investment Plan, 1976; Publication (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Box: 7, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Correctly Yours: A Guide for Secretaries, Stenographers, Typists, Publication (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Box: 7, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Box: 7, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Salaries Press Kit, 1986; Publication (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Box: 7, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention Rules, Publication (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Box: 7, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Talks Given at the First Annual Management Conference, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Box: 7, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Statements Made By Company Representatives At Public Hearings Before the Committee on Utilities of the City Council of the City of Chicago in Connection with the Application of the Commonwealth Edison Company for a New Franchise, Publication (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Box: 7, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: An Eventful Year, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 49)
    Author: Charles Y. Freeman
- Box: 7, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Excerpts from Letter Dated 1/20/48 by Francis X. Busch to Clarence P. Wagner, 1948; Publication (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Box: 7, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Company Information Sheet, 1951; Publication (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Box: 7, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Human Relations for Middle Management, 1954; Publication (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Box: 7, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: 1969 Ten Year Financial Review, 1970; Publication (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Box: 7, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: 1960 Financial Review: A Reflection of Efficiency, Publication (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Box: 7, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Employee Stock Purchase Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Box: 7, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: See You at Metropolitan Life, 1956; Publication (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Box: 7, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Opportunities for College Graduates in the Chicago and Northern Illinois Area, Publication (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Box: 7, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology: Commonwealth Edison Co. of Chicago 1946-1963, 1964; Publication (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Box: 7, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Edison Round Table 'Answer Corner' Subjects Index, 1952; Publication (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Box: 7, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: 1963 Financial Review, 1964; Publication (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Box: 7, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Employment Opportunities for Engineers, 1954; Publication (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Box: 7, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Disability Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Box: 7, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Employee Suggestion System, 1952; Publication (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Box: 7, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: 1974 Financial Review, 1975; Publication (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Box: 7, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: 1966 Financial Review, 1967; Publication (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Box: 7, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: The Challenge of Innovation, Publication (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Box: 7, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: A Medical Protection Plan for You and Your Family, 1973; Publication (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Box: 7, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: You and Your Pension, 1969; Publication (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Box: 7, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Retirement for Age, 1969; Publication (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Box: 8, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Welcome- Handbook, 1961; Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Box: 8, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Service Annuity System and Related Trust Agreement (As of 1/1/64)- Pensions, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Box: 8, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Statement on Discrimination in Employment, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Box: 8, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Financial Protection- Insurance, Group, Life (for employees of Commonwealth Edison Company), 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Box: 8, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Comprehensive Medical Plan For Employees of Commonwealth Edison Company, 1965; Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Box: 8, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan for Service Annuitants of Commonwealth Edison Company, 1966; Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Box: 8, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Educational Opportunities, 1955; Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Box: 8, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: First Aid- Instructor's Guide, 1955; Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Box: 8, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Employee Suggestion Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Box: 8, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Supervisors- Code For Supervision, 1955; Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Box: 8, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Handbook - It's Good To Know, 1952; Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Box: 8, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: First Aid, 1955; Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Box: 8, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Education- Second Semester Educational Opportunities for Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Box: 8, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Mutual Benefit Association- Benefit Plans and Organization, 1952; Publication (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Box: 8, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Pension Plans, 1959; Publication (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Box: 8, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Pension- Service Annuity System and Related Trust Agreement (As of 1/1/59), 1959; Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Box: 8, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules and Instructions, 1955; Publication (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Box: 8, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Protection Against Major Medical Expenses, 1955; Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Box: 8, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Comprehensive Medical Expense Insurance Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Box: 8, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: New Group Life Insurance, 1952; Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Box: 8, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Mutual Benefit Association- 8/4/52, 1953; Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Box: 8, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Employees Security Plan, 1971; Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Box: 8, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Retirement for Age, 1971; Publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Box: 8, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Management Employees Benefits, 1972; Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Box: 8, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Weekly Employee Benefits, 1972; Publication (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Box: 8, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan for Management Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Box: 8, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan for Weekly Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Box: 8, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Tuition Aid Program, 1967; Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Box: 8, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Retirement for Age, 1966; Publication (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Box: 8, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Disability Benefits- Employees Security Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Box: 8, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Uniform Group Insurance Plan For Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Box: 8, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan for Employees and Officers, 1950; Publication (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Box: 8, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Retirement for Age, 1961; Publication (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Box: 8, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Employees Security Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Box: 8, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan for Employees and Officers, 1953; Publication (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Box: 8, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Box: 8, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, 1954; Publication (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Box: 8, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Uniform Group Insurance Plan For Employees, 1958; Publication (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Box: 8, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Medical Care and Sickness Benefits, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Box: 8, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Basic Wage Progression Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Box: 8, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Employees Security Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Box: 8, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Retirement for Age, 1954; Publication (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Box: 8, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Employees Security Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Box: 8, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Retirement for Age, 1958; Publication (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Box: 8, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Uniform Group Insurance Plan For Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Box: 8, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Medical Care and Sickness Benefits, 1954; Publication (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Box: 8, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Retirement for Age, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Box: 8, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Tuition Aid Program, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Box: 8, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Uniform Group Insurance Plan For Employees, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Box: 8, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Retirement Program, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Box: 8, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Industry- You Questions About Niagara, 1952; Publication (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Box: 8, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Employment Recruiting, 1951; Publication (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Box: 8, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Monthly Investment Plan For The Employees of ConEdison, 1973; Publication (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Box: 8, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan For Eligible Dependents of Members, 1966; Publication (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Box: 8, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Information About the Monthly Investment Plan, 1967; Publication (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Box: 8, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan For Eligible Dependents of Members, 1967; Publication (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Box: 8, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Retirement Program, 1961; Publication (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Box: 8, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan For Monthly Employees and Their Families, 1961; Publication (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Box: 8, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Improved Continental Retirement Program- Pension, 1972; Publication (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Box: 8, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Top Management Chart, 1959; Publication (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Box: 8, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Department, 1959; Publication (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Box: 8, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Employee Merit Rating Report, 1953; Publication (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Box: 8, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation Summary, 1954; Publication (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Box: 8, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: General Pension Board, 1955; Publication (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Box: 8, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Basic Non-Contributory Salaried Pension Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Box: 8, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Performance Appraisal, 1956; Publication (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Box: 8, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Organization Development Program, 1954; Publication (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Box: 8, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Employment-Wages, 1952; Publication (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Box: 8, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: College Relations Program, 1954; Publication (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Box: 8, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Reports, 1950; Publication (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Box: 8, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Retirement Program, 1974; Publication (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Box: 8, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 8, Folder 72)